A Guide to the Bell, Kent, Cloyd, Withrow Family Collection, 1780-1998
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- Gordon Cloyd Bell, Jr. Papers, 1921-1967
  - Correspondence To, 1938-1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence From, 1962-1967, n.d. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Pilot Logs, 1941-1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Pilot Rating Book and Field Manuals, 1941-1943 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Patriotic Booklets, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Military Documents, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Safe Conduct Leaflet, version distributed December 1944-April 1945 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 40,000 Black Panthers of the 66th Division, c.1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Bank Statements and Bills, 1942-1965 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Land Deeds and Legal Documents, 1951-1963 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Tax Documents, 1957-1962 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Personal Items, n.d. (Box 12)
- David Kent Bell Papers, 1925-1978
  - Personal Items - Birth Certificate, Identifications, Pamphlets, and Newspaper Clippings, 1925-1955 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Education - Report Cards, Tests, and Programs, 1932-1946 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence To, October 1938-January 1944 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence To, April 1945-August 1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence From, October 1943-October 1945 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Military Documents, 1943-1945 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Military Documents, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Diplomas and Certificates, 1944-1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Financial Records - Receipts, 1943-1961 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Insurance Documents, 1947-1959 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Bell Family Papers, 1834-1841
  - James Bell - Bills of Sale, 1834-1841 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Mary Withrow Bell - Correspondence, March 27, 1917-November 8, 1918 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Mary Withrow Bell - Correspondence, December 1918-March 1937, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Mary Withrow Bell - Bank Statements and Receipts, 1925-1933 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Mary Withrow Bell and Annie Withrow - Land Deeds and Surveys, 1929-1934 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Mary Withrow Bell Estate, c.1938-1942 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Andrew Bell - Birth Certificate and Report Cards, 1932, 1939-1941 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Andrew Bell - Correspondence, 1941-1943 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Francis Bell (1864-1939) Estate, 1939-1942 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Francis Bell (1864-1939) Estate, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Ellen Howe Bell Magill and Family - Newspaper Clippings, Programs, and Correspondence, 1957-1969 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Bell Family, 1938-1941 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- James Withrow Papers, 1848-1910
  - Contracts, Correspondence, and Newspaper Clippings, 1848-1899 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Checks and Receipts, 1853-1904 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Money Orders, Debt Statements, Account Books and Statements, 1859-1901 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Estate, 1901-1910 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Edgar D. Withrow Papers, 1864-1936
  - Personal Correspondence, 1864-1899, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Greenbrier Light Infantry Grays, 1878-1882 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - "This Wedded Life", 1886 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records
    - Statements of Debt, 1873-1912 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Receipts, 1876-1898 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Receipts, 1900-1913 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Bank of Lewisburg Account Books, 1877-1904 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Checks, 1879-1902 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Contracts and Legal Documents, 1880-1906 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Tax Payments, 1881-1914 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Land Deeds, December 1881-September 1915 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Account Statements, 1881-1923 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence, 1882-1902 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1904-1911, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Money Orders, 1884-1892 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Account Booklets, 1884-1892 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Insurance Documents, 1885-1914 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Agricultural Implement Sales, 1889-1892 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Product Information and Lists, 1893, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Checkbooks, 1893-1895 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Checkbooks, 1896-1897 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Checkbooks, 1898-1906 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Ledger Books, 1893-1918 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Ledger Books, 1928-1936, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Bank of Radford Statements, April 1898-1899 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - State Personal Property Interrogatories, 1900-1914 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Estate, 1927 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Journal, 1883-1890 (Box 17)
- Annie Withrow Papers, 1889-1981
  - Personal Items, 1889-1973 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "The Greenbrier", 1908 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1928-1945 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1946-1970, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Land Deeds and Legal Documents, 1929-1969 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Guest Book, 1978-1981 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Withrow Family Papers, 1870-1941
  - James Withrow and Son - Money Orders and Debt Statements, 1870-1893 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - James Withrow and Son - Account Booklets and Statements, 1873-1893 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - James Withrow and Son - Receipts, 1880-1895 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Withrow and Cary - Business Records, 1873 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Hudson and Withrow - Business Records, 1873-1875 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Heber K. Withrow - Business Records, 1885-1897 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Mary Renick Withrow, 1888-1915 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Withrow Family - Financial Records, 1889-1911 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Helen Withrow, July 25, 1903 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Mary E. Withrow - Report Cards, Certificates, and "Appletons' Standard Elementary Geography", 1903-1911 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Mary J. Withrow, 1905-1910 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Letitia Withrow, 1909-1920 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Withrow Place, 1914-1989 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Letters from "Withrow Tourist Home", 1929-1941 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Withrow Family - Newspaper Clippings, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Ledger - James Withrow and Son, 1873-1888 (Box 16)
  - Withrow Family, 1854-1934 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Withrow Family - Education, 1909-1912 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Kent Family Papers, 1814-1881
  - James Randal Kent - Correspondence, September 1814-February 20, 1881 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - James Randal Kent - Land Surveys, March 1815 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - James Randal Kent - Debt Statements and Receipts, 1816-1857 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - James Randal Kent - Contracts and Agreements, 1817-1842 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - James Randal Kent - Account Statements, September 1829-May 20, 1850 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - James Randal Kent - Land Warrants, March 31, 1840 and July 29, 1840 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - David Fenton and James Randal Kent Partnerships, 1838 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - David Fenton Kent - Receipts and Debt Statements, 1820-1850, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - David Fenton Kent - Legal and Military Documents, 1830-1846 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - David Fenton Kent - Correspondence, 1840-1849 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - David Fenton Kent - Account Statements, 1841-1849 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - David F. Kent and Thomas Miller - Account Statements and Money Orders, 1849, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - David F. Kent and Thomas Miller Daybook, February-November 1849 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Letter to "Missis Kents" and Joseph Kent - Account Statements, April 27, 1851 and 1816 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Daybook - Springfield, 1803-1851 (Box 13)
  - Ledger - David Fenton Kent, 1840-1845 (Box 14)
  - Journal - David Fenton Kent, 1842-1845 (Box 15)
  - David Fenton Kent, 1838-c.1847 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Cloyd Family Papers, 1792-1866
  - Gordon Cloyd - Land Surveys, April 5, 1792-March 8, 1827 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Gordon Cloyd - Correspondence, 1794-1830 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Gordon Cloyd - Receipts and Land Transfers, August 29, 1795-January 12, 1825 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Gordon Cloyd - Account and Debt Statements, 1822-1831 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Mary Cloyd - Account Statement, 1813 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - James M. Cloyd - Debt Statements and Receipts, 1855-1866 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - James M. Cloyd - Account Statements, 1861-1866 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - James M. Cloyd - Confederate Military Materials, 1862 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - James M. Cloyd - Correspondence, January 23, 1863 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Joseph L. Cloyd - Land Patent, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Cloyd Family, 1824-1862 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Gordon Cloyd - Correspondence, 1793-1821 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Other Family Papers, 1780-1998
  - James McCorkle, 1785-1899 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Preston Family, 1787-1841 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - James Watson - Land Deed, 1796 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - James Montgomery - Will, 1808 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Mathews Family, 1809-1872 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Wygal Family - Deeds, 1817-1844 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Brotherhood Family, 1823-1830 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - James W. Shields, 1843-1845 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Renick Family, 1852-1902 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Estate of Virginia Woodson, 1870-1899 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - J.T. Trollinger - "Some Recollections of an Old Confederate", n.d. (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Larken Cleaveland - Poem, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Bell and Withrow Family Photographs, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Wygal Family, 1824-1852 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Land Warrants, 1780-1813 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Land Sales and Surveys, 1783-1876 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1785-1899 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Will, September 1790 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Receipts, 1803-1888 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Regimental Orders, 1812-1818 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Regimental Listings - 86th Virginia, April 29, 1816 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Debt and Claim Listings, 1817-1837 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Legal Documents, 1817-1902 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Tax Payments, 1822-1913 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Account Statements and Work Counts, 1824-1891 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Debt Statements, 1870-1897 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Wedding Announcements and Obituaries, 1889-1998 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Newspaper Clippings, 1939-1976, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Land Surveys and Deeds, 1783-1882 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Other Materials - Photo of Confederate Memorial, Estate Listing of James Montgomery, Thompson Family Agreement, and Memorandum of Debts, 1808-1906 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Regimental Listings for the 35th, 75th, 86th, and 108th Virginia Regiments, 1816-1819 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Maps, 1929-1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Other Materials, 1901-1997
  - Women's Magazines, 1901-1914 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Presbyterian Church Publications, 1914-1973 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Programs and Brochures, 1919-1954 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - New Dublin Presbyterian Church - Church Booklets, 1939-1997 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Polytechnic Institute - Booklets, 1942-1949 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Railroad Brochures, 1944 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - New Dublin Presbyterian Church - Newspaper Clippings and Photographs, 1959-1962 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Unidentified Ledger Pages, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Farming Books, n.d. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Unidentified Photographs (2 folders), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 8-9)